export const questionL1 = [
    {
      question: '1 + 1',
      choices: ['2', '21', '1', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      question: '2 + 1',
      choices: ['2', '3', '1', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: '3',
    },
    {
      question: '3 + 1',
      choices: ['2', '21', '4', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: '4',
    },
    {
      question: '12 + 1',
      choices: ['2', '21', '1', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
        question: '9 + 4',
        choices: ['21', '12', '1', '13'],
        correctAnswer: '13',
      },
      {
        question: '8 + 7',
        choices: ['2', '21', '1', '15'],
        correctAnswer: '15',
      },
      {
        question: '2 + 9',
        choices: ['11', '9', '1', '3'],
        correctAnswer: '11',
      },
      {
        question: '3 + 6',
        choices: ['6', '9', '4', '8'],
        correctAnswer: '9',
      },
      {
        question: '7 + 9',
        choices: ['4', '5', '21', 'None of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
      },
      {
          question: '9 + 9',
          choices: ['21', '18', '2', '32'],
          correctAnswer: '18',
        },
  ]
  export default questionL1





  